http://www.funkypool.com/privacy

UsernamePassword
SignupForgot Password
HomePlayRankingsTournaPoints Scores8 Ball Arcade Games9 Ball Arcade Games8 Ball Billiards Games9 Ball Billiards Games8 Ball Pool UK GamesKiller Pool GamesStraight Pool GamesRandom TournamentsOverall ScoresMini Golf GamesTournamentsUpcomingAvailable to Join (0)In Play (0)FinishedForumHelpSnooker Games
Find Player
Privacy Policy This Policy relates only to our ("funky pool") online information collection and use practices. At funky pool we recognize that many consumers who visit our web sites are concerned about any information they provide us on-line, and how we maintain and use this information. To address these concerns and to demonstrate our commitment to privacy, especially for children who visit our sites, we have developed and implemented this Privacy Policy. This Policy relates only to our online information collection and use practices. As this policy may change from time to time, we encourage you to periodically check it. In short, we do the following:We only collect personally identifiable information that you voluntarily and knowingly provide us, with the exception of IP address, used for monitoring of multiusing;We use the information that you provide us only for the purpose(s) for which you specifically provided it or for specific additional purposes for which we receive your prior consent;We do not share any information you provide us with anyone outside of funky pool, with exception of the opt-in choices on sign-up;We use a technology called cookies to enhance your experience on our site (cookies are used for the "remember user" feature);We provide you with choice and control over the collection and use of any personally identifiable information that you provide us on-line, and a means for updating, correcting or removing this informationWe will periodically send you email if you opt-in to receive email. If you do not want to receive email from us in the future, please let us know by specifying in the Edit Profile section.We use 3rd party advertisement servers to try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policies of:GoogleGoogle uses the DART cookie to serve you relevant advertising based on visits to this and other sites on the Internet.You may opt out of using the cookie on the Google privacy information page.We allow all registered visitors access to all information (including proprietary information) that we maintain about them (Using "Edit Profile")How To Contact Us If you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy or your dealings with funky pool, please contact us.
© funky pool games 2020 TermsPrivacyHelpContact us
